jpgmag.com 2019-02-23

# JPG: About: Privacy policy

### Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy discloses the online privacy practices for JPG and applies to the information we collect through http://jpgmag.com (the “Site”). By accessing and/or using the Site, you are consenting to the collection, storage and disclosure of data as described in this Privacy Policy.

JPG reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, update or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes to this Policy on this page so you can readily review the most current version. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the bottom of this Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how JPG is helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of this Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

#### IP addresses

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When a user requests a page from the Site, our servers will log the user's current IP address. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site.

#### Cookies

This website uses cookies. A "cookie" is a small text file that contains a string of alphanumeric characters. There are two types of cookies that may be used: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the "Cookies" folder on your computer and remains in this "Cookies" folder after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer's memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut off your computer. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. If you disable cookies, your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site.

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. 

#### Personal Information

When you opt in to fill out our contact form on the Site, we will ask you to provide us with information, including your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and mailing address ("Personal Information")

#### Use of Personal Information

We will not sell, trade or otherwise provide Personal Information to any third party. We will use Personal Information only for the purposes of contacting you and sending you information regarding the Site and JPG services. We may compile and provide aggregate statistics about our Site visitors to third parties, but these statistics will not include any Personal Information.

Personal Information collected on the Site will be stored and processed in the United States and by using the Site, you expressly consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

#### Integrity of Your Personal Information

JPG is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. You have the right to access and correct the Personal Information you have provided by contacting us using our contact form.

#### Protection of Children’s Personal Information

JPGMag.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

#### Use of Submission Information

Any other information other than Personal Information we collect through the Site (including, without limitation, feedback regarding the Site or any comments, ideas and suggestions you provide) is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "Submission Information."

As described in our Terms of Use, JPG does not accept or collect Submission Information on a confidential or proprietary basis. Consequently, we are free to use Submission Information for any purpose whatsoever.

#### Disclosures to Third Parties

Because JPG does not accept or collect Submission Information on a confidential or proprietary basis, from time to time JPG may disclose your Submission Information to third parties, including, without limitation, our consultants, our representatives and our affiliated companies.

#### Disclosures for Legal Reasons

JPG will also disclose Submission Information and Personal Information when it believes, in its sole discretion, that the law requires such disclosure or that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; protect and defend the rights or property of JPG or others; or act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the public or the users of the Site.

#### Links

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by JPG. Other websites (including those that we may link to) may have their own policies.

JPG has no responsibility for or control over the information-collection practices of any other third party websites.

#### Notification of Changes

If JPG is going to use Personal Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Site, JPG will notify those from whom JPG has collected Personal Information via e-mail. You will then have a choice as to whether or not we may continue using your Personal Information in this different manner. In addition, if JPG decides to make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect Personal Information already collected through the Site, we will post a notice on the Site notifying users of the change.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our contact form.

NAI - <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>
